A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Art, Series C FA340
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Collection Inventories, 4
  - Set 4
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 8, 30.103 (Box 5, Folder 102)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.101 (Box 6, Folder 103)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.101, 30.102 (Box 6, Folder 104)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.102 (Box 6, Folder 105)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.102 (Box 6, Folder 106)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.102 (Box 6, Folder 107)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 9, 30.102 (Box 6, Folder 108)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 10, 30.206 (Box 6, Folder 109)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 10, 30.206 (Box 6, Folder 110)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 10, 30.206, 30.207 (Box 6, Folder 111)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 10, 30.209 (Box 6, Folder 112)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 10, 30.210 (Box 6, Folder 113)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 114)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 115)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 116)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 117)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 118)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 11, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 119)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.103, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 120)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 121)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 122)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 123)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 124)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 12, 30.105 (Box 6, Folder 125)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 13, 30.102, 30.201 (Box 7, Folder 126)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 13, 30.201 (Box 7, Folder 127)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 13, 30.201 (Box 7, Folder 128)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 13, 30.201 (Box 7, Folder 129)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 14, 30.105 (Box 7, Folder 130)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 14, 30.105 (Box 7, Folder 131)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 14, 30.105 (Box 7, Folder 132)
    - Foxhall Road - Volume 14, 30.105 (Box 7, Folder 133)
- Printed Material, 1935-1978; 5; 17 Cubic Feet
  This subseries contains auction catalogs, exhibit catalogs, art books and other printed items related to Mr. Rockefeller's interest in art. He read art auction catalogs and gallery brochures as commonly as some people read novels. He usually took some with him on his travels, to scan when he had a free moment. Of particular interest are the auction catalogs that are notated by Mr. Rockefeller to indicate which items he was interested in acquiring. The notations, which were directed to Mrs. Uht, include the maximum amount he was willing to pay for each item. Mrs. Uht sometimes reviewed the catalogs before Mr. Rockefeller did and placed paper clips on pages with items that she thought he might want to purchase.
  The exhibit catalogs are primarily from the Museum of Modern Art and the Museum of Primitive Art, both of which he was closely associated with. Mrs. Uht also tried to keep a copy of everything that was published regarding works owned by Mr. Rockefeller, particularly exhibit catalogs that included items borrowed from his collection. There is also about one cubic foot of miscellaneous art books, some in languages other than English.
  There are eight volumes of Library Catalogs, which primarily record the location of each of Mr. Rockefeller's many art books. The last two volumes record the location of etchings and drawings owned by Mr. Rockefeller.
  Finally, there are 23 volumes of appraisals of portions of Mr. Rockefeller's collections conducted annually from 1962 to 1976. This was done by the Fine Arts Valuation Service, headed by Gustave Gilbert. The works included in each volume are arranged alphabetically by artist and then by title. A catalog number is included as well as the value of the work. Some notations were made showing that an item was going to leave the collection (pledged) or had already left the collection (canceled).
  The Museum of Primitive Art books, Museum of Modern Art books, and miscellaneous art books have been included in the Rockefeller Archive Center library card catalog. Access to RAC library material is available to onsite researchers only.
  - Kykuit Collection Catalog, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Kykuit Collection Photography, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kykuit Collection - Benjamin Franklin Portrait, 1936-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kykuit Collection - Sculpture, 1970s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kykuit Collection - Wunderlich Appraisals at Archive Center (CLOSED FOLDER), 1970s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Kykuit Collection - Wunderlich Appraisals, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Kykuit Collection - Sculpture and Playhouse Pieces, c. mid-1970s (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Kykuit Collection - Joint Art Appraisals, 1973, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kykuit Collection - Stone Restoration, 1969-1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Kykuit Collection - Miscellaneous, 1960-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries Correspondence, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries - Photo Catalog, March 1970 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries - Photo Catalog, May 1970 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries - Photo Catalog, November 1970 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries - Catalogs (1), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Ralph M. Chait Galleries - Catalogs (2), 1974 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Antique Porcelain Company Correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Antique Porcelain Company Correspondence, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - J. A. Lloyd Hyde, 1967-February 1969 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - J. A. Lloyd Hyde, April-September 1969 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - J. A. Lloyd Hyde, October 1969-1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Correspondence, 1967-1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London (and affiliates) Catalogs, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, 1971, June 1973 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, August-December 1973 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, April 1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, July 1974 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, October-November 1974 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, December 1974 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, March 1975 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, November 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, December 1975 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Sotheby and Co. of London Catalogs, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Christie's Catalogs, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Christie's Catalogs, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Christie's Catalogs, July and November 1973 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Christie's Catalogs, December 1973 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Christie's Catalogs, 1974 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Christie's Catalogs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Christie's Catalogs, March and July 1976 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Christie's Catalogs, December 1976 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Christie's Catalogs, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Correspondence, 1968-1975 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, April and September 1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, October 1970 (Box 6, Folder 48)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, November-December 1970 (Box 6, Folder 49)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, January-March 1971 (Box 6, Folder 50)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, May-December 1971 (Box 6, Folder 51)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, April 1972 (Box 6, Folder 52)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, May 1972 (Box 6, Folder 53)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, June-October 1972 (Box 6, Folder 54)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, February 1973 (Box 6, Folder 55)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, May and September 1973 (Box 6, Folder 56)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, November 1-21, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, November 24-29, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, February-March 1974 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, May 1974 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, June-July 1974 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, October 3-18, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, October 20-22, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, October 31, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, November 1974 (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, May and October 1975 (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, November 1975 (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, December 1975 (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Sotheby Parke-Bernet Catalogs, 1977 (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Palais Galliera Catalog, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 71)
- Canceled Art Files, 1949-1979; 6; 10 Cubic Feet
  When Mr. Rockefeller parted with a piece of art, through gift, damage, or sale, the piece was recorded as "canceled" and the records concerning it were moved to the Canceled Art File. The file usually notes the name of the individual or institution each work went to, as well as the price for those works that were sold. This subseries also includes a photo file of canceled modern and nonmodern works.
  Restriction-Material is open for scholarly research with prior archival review for material related to living members of the Rockefeller family.
  - Sections 1-50 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (A) (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Abularach, Rodolfo; Altdorfer; Anuszkiewicz, Richard; Appel, Karen; Armitage; Arp, Jean; Asahina, Takashi
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (A) (Box 1, Folder 2a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Bacci; Balla, Giacomo; Baier; Banerjee, Bimal; Barlach; Baskin, Leonard; Beall, C.C.; Beaudin, Andre; Bennet, Rainey; Berge, Dorothy
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 3a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Berrocal; Bonnard; Boterf, Check; Brancusi, Constantin
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 4a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Braque; Bremmer, Al. R; Brooks, James; Budwick, SG; Burchfield, Charles; Bury, Pol; Butler
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (B) (Box 1, Folder 5a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (C) (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Calder, Alexander; Capograssi; Capurro, Enrique; Chadwick, Lynn; Chagall, Marc; Chinas, Zeichnungen nech Wu Tao-tze; Chinese (no artist name); Chinni
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (C) (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Chirino, Martin; Christie, Howard Chandler; Coggeshall, G.; Colla, Ettore; Corneille; Colton, Maurice; Consuegra, Hugh; Cooper, Warren; Coughline, Marion; Craig, Martin; Crawford, Alice Berle; Currier, Nathaniel
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (D) (Box 2, Folder 8)
    Davie, Allen; Day, Worden deChirico, Georgio
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (D) (Box 2, Folder 9)
    DeChirico, Giorgio
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (D) (Box 2, Folder 10)
    Dega, Edgar; De la Fresnaye; DeLamonica, Roberto; Delvaux, Paul; Demuth, Charles; Derain
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (D) (Box 2, Folder 11)
    Diederen; DiSpirito; Droungas, Achilles; Duccio; Duchamp, Marcel; Dufour, Bernard
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (E) (Box 2, Folder 12)
    Edion, Henri; Ekong, Afi; Ekstrom; Engman, RObert; Epstein, Jacob; Erni, Hans; Ernest, Max
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (F) (Box 2, Folder 13)
    Faulkner, Frank; Feininger, Lyonel; Fernandez, Louis; Fink, Herbert; Flavin, Dan; Fortier; Fragonard; Fontana, Cristo; Frankenthaler, Helen; Frasconi, Antonio; Frasier; Frazer, Donald H.
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (F) (Box 2, Folder 13a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 2, Folder 14a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 15)
    Gleizes, Albert
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    Goodnough, Robert; Gordon; Greenly, Colin; Gorky, Arshile
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 17)
    Gray, Cleve; Grausman, Cleve; Griz, Juan; Gugliemi, Louis; Gunther, Max; Guttuso; Greek (no artist name)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 18)
    Greek (no artist name)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 18a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 3, Folder 19)
    Gottlieb
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 4, Folder 20)
    Guston, Philip
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (G) (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (H) (Box 4, Folder 22)
    Haas, Terry; Hakumaki; Hanspers; Hartung, Hans; Hayes, David; Hayter, Stanley William; Heke, William; Helion, Jean
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (H) (Box 4, Folder 22a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (H) (Box 4, Folder 23)
    Harnett, William
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (H) (Box 4, Folder 24)
    Herrera; Hirsch, Stefan; Hepworth, Barbara; Hogarth, Paul; Hosiasson; Hmme, Alice; Hnizdovsky, Jaques; Hugo; Hunziker; Hurtado, Angel; Hyde, Scott
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (H) (Box 4, Folder 24a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (I-J) (Box 5, Folder 25)
    Ihenfeld, Klaus; Indiana, Robert; Ivanijcki, Olja
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (I-J) (Box 5, Folder 26)
    Jaeckel, Willi; Japanese (no artist name)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (I-J) (Box 5, Folder 27)
    Jawlensky, Alexej; Johns, Jasper; Johnson, Daniel LeRue; Johnston, Ynez
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (K) (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Kandinsky, Wassily; Karoly, Frederic; Kimball; Kimura, Shigeru; Kirchner, Ernest Ludwig; Klee, Paul
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (K) (Box 5, Folder 29)
    Kline, Franz; Knipschild, Robert; Kohn, Gabe; Krasinski, Edward
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (K) (Box 5, Folder 29a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (K) (Box 6, Folder 30)
    deKooning, Willem
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (K) (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Kornburst, Leo
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Lachaise, Gaston; Lam, Wilfredo; Laurent, Robert; Lawrence, Jacob; Liberman, Alexander
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 32a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Leger, Fernand
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 33a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Lichenstein, Roy; Lipchitz, Jacques; Lipton, Seymour; Litto, Frank; Lockwood, George; Lorne, Naomi; Louis, Morris; Lowe, Maxine; Lytle, Richard
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 6, Folder 34a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (L) (Box 7, Folder 35)
    Liberman, Alexander
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 36)
    Mack, Heinz; Magnelli, ALberto; Magritte, Rene; Maillol; Manolo; Marca, Relli; Marks; Marini; Masson, Andre; Mathieu, George; Matisse, Henri
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 36a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 37)
    Matisse, Henri
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 37a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 38)
    Mills, Roland; Minnie; Mirko; Miro; Modigliani; Mondrain, Piet; Montenegro, Roberto; Morris, Robert; Motherwell, Robert; Muccini, Marcello; Mundt, Ernest
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (M) (Box 7, Folder 38a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (N-O) (Box 8, Folder 39)
    Nadelman, Elie; Napoli, Giuseppe; Nicholson, Ben; Noguchi; Obin; Ocampo, Miguel; Okada, Kenzo; Ozenfant, Amedee
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso) (Box 8, Folder 40)
    96 Etchings; Boy on Horseback; Composition Blue au Possin; Etude de Femme; Garon a Cheval; Girl with Mandolin; Guitar and Fruit Basket
    - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso - Guitar on Table) (Box 8, Folder 40a)
      Picasso, Pablo
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso) (Box 8, Folder 41)
    Guitar on Table
    - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso) (Box 8, Folder 41a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso) (Box 8, Folder 42)
    Head in Browns and Black; La Bouteille de Bass; Le Cirque; Leda; Les Bougneuses; Minotauromachy; Owl; Red and White Owl; POrtrait of Fora Maar
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Picasso) (Box 8, Folder 43)
    Sheet of Studies of Nudes and Bulls' Study of a Hand; Sylvetter Sur Pond Rouge; Terra cotta; Verres et Fruits; Vie Mare; Visite at'atelier
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (P) (Box 9, Folder 44)
    Pedroza, Paul; Peterdi, Gabor; Pignon, G; Poliakoff, Serge; Pollack, Jackson; Portinari, Candido
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (P) (Box 9, Folder 45)
    Peto
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Q-R) (Box 9, Folder 46)
    Raussmulla; Redon; Reinhold, Nono; Reynal. Jean; Rickey, George; Rinshelwood; Robinson, GLadys Lloyd; Romano, Clare; Rosenquist, James; Roth, David
    - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Q-R) (Box 9, Folder 46a)
      Reynal, Jeanne
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Q-R) (Box 9, Folder 47)
    Rothko, Mark
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (Q-R) (Box 9, Folder 47a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 9, Folder 48)
    Saff, David; Salisbury, Frank O.; Sanders, Ludwig; Santomaso, Giuseppe; Savelli, Angelo
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 9, Folder 48a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 10, Folder 49)
    Schanker, Louis; Schenck; Schmidt; Scipone; Seliger, Charles; Sligmann, Kurt; Shahn, Ben; Sheeler, Charles; Sherman; Sills, Joyce; Skaggs, Robert L.
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 10, Folder 50)
    Smith, David; Solbert, Ronni; Sonenberg, Jack; Sowers, Robert; Spencer, Niles; Spruance, Benton; Stahly, Francois; Stankiewicz, Richard
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 10, Folder 50a)
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (S) (Box 10, Folder 51)
    Stolen, Oddbjorn; Sugai, Kumi; Sutherland, Graham Vivian; Szyszlo, Fernando
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (T) (Box 10, Folder 52)
    Takahasi; Takeda; Takis; Tamayo; Tanguey, Yves; Tappan, Diana; Tauber-Arp, Sophie H.; Tchelitchew; Pavel; Tinguely, Jean; Tomlin; Tomneyama, K.; Tooker, George; Torres-Garcia, Joaquin; Toulouse-Lautrec, Henri de
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (U-V) (Box 10, Folder 53)
    Uchima; Uecker; Unknown; Unknown; Valenti; Van Gogh, Vincent; Vasarely, Victor; Vesdignani, Reufo; Vickrey, Robert; Viesulas; Vlaminck; Vuilliamy, Justin Edward
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (W) (Box 11, Folder 54)
    Wagenar, Koosje; Wagner, Carl; Warhol, Andy; Weiss, Emil Rudolf; Wilson, A.L.; Winner
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (X-Z) (Box 11, Folder 55)
    Yoran, Yehude; Youngerman, Jack; Zeidman, Robert
  - Alphabetical File, By Artist (X-Z) (Box 11, Folder 55a)
  - Photo Files (A - Archipenko) (Box 11, Folder 56)
    Abeles, Sigmund; Abrams, Ross; Abularach, Rodolfo; Albers, Josef; Album; Alexander, J.E.; Alix, G.; d'Amico; d'Andlau, Helene; Antonio, Jose; Antreasian, Garo Z.; Anuszkiewicz, Richard; Appel, Karel; Archipenko, Alexander
  - Photo Files (Armitage - Avati) (Box 11, Folder 57)
    Armitage; Kenneth; Arp, Jean; Asahina, Takashi; Asaka, M.; Asawa, Ruth; Asio; Avati, Mario
  - Photo Files (B - Beckman) (Box 11, Folder 58)
    B...; Bacci; Bacon, Peggy; Baier, Jean; Bakon, Yehuda; Balla, Giacomo; Bandila, Albert; Banerjee, Bimal; Bardone, Guy; Barlach, Ernest; Baskin, Leonard; Bate, Stanley; Baziotes, William; Beaudin, Andre; Beavior, P.; Beckmann, Max
  - Photo Files (Behrens - Bennett) (Box 11, Folder 59)
    Behrens, Peter; Belden, Monte; Bender, C. Whitney; Bennett, Rainey
  - Photo Files (Bennett) (Box 12, Folder 60)
    Bennett, Rainey
  - Photo Files (Bennish - Bo) (Box 12, Folder 61)
    Bennish, Grace; Benvenuti, Mario; Ben-zion; Berge, Dorothy; Berlin, Beatrice; Berman, Eugene; Bernard, Emile; Berrocal, Miguel; Berry; Emile; Bertoia, Harry; Biddle, Michael; Biese, Gerth; Blanchard, Sisson; Blaustein, Al; Bo, Lars
  - Photo Files (Boccioni - Boyer) (Box 12, Folder 62)
    Boccioni, Umberto; Bone, Freda; Bonnard, Pierre; Botello, A.; Bouche, Louise; Boulanger, Gustave; Bouts, Bernard; Bowman, Dorothy; Boyer, Grindage
  - Photo Files (Brady - Braustein) (Box 12, Folder 63)
    Brancusi, Constantin; Braque, Georges; Braustein, Cy
  - Photo Files (Brazilian - Butler) (Box 12, Folder 64)
    Brazilian (no artist name); Breinin, Raymond; Bremmer, Al R.; Breuer, Florian; Brierre, Murat; Briggs, Ernest; Brooks, James; Brown, Carlyle; Brown, Judith; Brown, Kathan; Browning, Colleen; Bryen, Camille; Bucknell, W.H.W; Budwick; SG; Burchfield, Charles; Burrage, Mildred; Bury, Pol; Butler, Reg
  - Photo Files (Calder - Capogrossi) (Box 12, Folder 65)
    Calder, Alexander; Callery, Mary; Capogrossi, Giuseppe
  - Photo Files (Capurro - Chadwick) (Box 12, Folder 66)
    Capurro, E. Castell; Carriere, Eugene; Caruso, Bruno; Castellanos, Julio; Castellon, Federico; Cavael, Rolf; Cezanne, Paul; Chadwick, Lynn
  - Photo Files (Chagall - Consuegra) (Box 13, Folder 67)
    Chagall, Marc; Charies, Oliver; Charlot, Jean; Childs, Bernard; Chinni, Peter; deChirico, Giorgio; Chirino, Martin; Chisolm, T.H.; Christensen, Dan; Christi, Frank; Christoforou, John; Christy, Howard Chandler; Chryssa; Cickvsky, Nicolai; Citron, Minna; Clark, Pat; Cloar, Carroll; Cohen, George M.;Colas-Guerin, J.; Cole, Timothy; Colla, Ettore; Colton, Maurice; Coman, Charlotte Buell; Comtois, Ulysses; Conover, Robert; Consuegra, Hugh
  - Photo Files (Cooper - Cross) (Box 13, Folder 68)
    Coper, Warren; Corita, Sister Mary; Corneille; Coughline, Marion; Coughlin, Jack; Courtwright, Robert; Craig, Martin; Creaser, John Will; Cristiano, Renato; Cross, Henri Edmound
  - Photo Files (Dalengord - Denis) (Box 13, Folder 69)
    Delenoord, Jenny; Daley, Kenneth G.; D'Amico, Mabel; Dang, Le Ba; Daumier, Honore; Davidson, Jo; Davie, Alan; Davies, Arthur B.; Day, Worden; Dean, Albner J.; Debany, Edythe B.; Debenjak, Riko; Degas, Edgar; Dehn, Adolf; Delvaux, Paul; Demuth, Charles; Demyan, Jack
  - Photo Files (Denis - Dickenson) (Box 13, Folder 70)
    Denis, Maurice; Derain, Andre; Deshaies, Arthur; Dey, Rani; D'harnoncourt, Rene; DiChirico, Giorgio; Dickenson, Sidney Edward
  - Photo Files (Dierderen - Dwight) (Box 13, Folder 71)
    Diederen, Jef; Dikkenboer, Daniel; Dispirito, Henry; Donnelly, Lucy; Dorlhiac, C.; Dows, Stephen Olin; Drewes, Werner; Drinkard, Richard W.; Droungas, Achilles; Dubuffet, Jean; Duchamp, Marcel; Dufour, Bernard; Dufy, Raoul; Dumitresco, Natalie; Dwight, Mabel
  - Photo Files (E) (Box 13, Folder 72)
    Edion, Henri; Eglau, Otto; Ekong, Afi; Ekstrom, Arne; Elenbass, William; Emmet, Lydia; Engel, Jules; Engman, Robert; Epstein, Jacob; Ep'tycien; Erni, Hans; Ernest, Jimmy; Ernest, Max; Escher, M. Evans, Merlyn
  - Photo Files (Fahnestock - Florsheim) (Box 13, Folder 73)
    Fahnestock, Wallace Weir; Faille, Carl A.; Fantin-Latour, Henri; Fazzini, Pericle; Feeler, Paul; Feininger, Lyonel; Feldman, Eugene; Felten, Major; Fernandez, Louis; Fiene, Ernest; Feron, Louis; Figari, Pedro; Fink, Herbet; Fink, Sheldon; Finnish; Fischer, Harris; Flavin, Dan; Floiloff, C.; Flor, Eduard; Florsheim, Richard
  - Photo Files (Fontana - Frost) (Box 14, Folder 74)
    Fontana, Lucio; Fornas, Leander; Forrel; Forrester, Patricia Tobacco; Forseberg, James; Forsberg, Jan; Fortier, Michel; Fracarossi; Joseph; Francis, Sam; Franck, Frederick; Frankenthaler, Helen; Frasconi, Antonio; Fraser, Donald Hamilton; Freidlander; Frost, Arthur Burdett
  - Photo Files (Gabo - Glarner) (Box 14, Folder 75)
    Gabo, Naum; Gambling; William T.; Gatch, Lee; Ghika, Nikos Hatzikyriakos; Giacometti, Alberto; Gilbertson, Boris; Gilioli, Emile; Gobbi, Edward; Glarner, Fritz
  - Photo Files (Glasco - Goodnough) (Box 14, Folder 76)
    Glasco, Joseph; Gleizes, Albert; Goeschl, Roland; Gonzalez; Guillermo; Gonzalez, Julio; Goodnough, Robert